<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Victor Zhang | Full Stack &amp; Mobile Engineer | From Idea to App Store</title><description>Full Stack and Mobile Engineer specializing in SwiftUI, React Native, React, and Node.js. Creating exceptional digital experiences.</description><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/</link><item><title>Choosing the Right JavaScript Data Visualization Framework: Insights and Comparisons</title><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/javascript-data-visualization-frameworks/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/javascript-data-visualization-frameworks/</guid><description>A comprehensive guide comparing popular JavaScript data visualization frameworks to help you choose the right tool for your project</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG): The Power of Hybrid Search</title><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/retrieval-augmented-generation-rag/</guid><description>An in-depth exploration of RAG, comparing vector and keyword retrieval, understanding hybrid search strategies, and why RAG is essential for modern LLM applications.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Board Game AI Development: From Minimax to Modern Deep Learning</title><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/board-game-ai-development/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/board-game-ai-development/</guid><description>Exploring the evolution of artificial intelligence in board games, from classical algorithms to modern machine learning approaches</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Essential React State Management: Common Pitfalls and Best Practices</title><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/react-dev-tips/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/react-dev-tips/</guid><description>Learn critical React state management patterns and avoid common mistakes that lead to bugs and performance issues</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vibe Coding with Git Worktrees: A Playbook Most Devs Are Missing</title><link>https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/worktree-refactor-playbook/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://zywkloo.github.io/blog/worktree-refactor-playbook/</guid><description>Most people vibe-code with one model in one branch. Here is how to use multiple models, git worktrees, and a phased workflow to ship refactors without breaking everything.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>